(Leonard:)I'm glad you had a
nice time with Amy.
(Sheldon:)Me, too. It's comforting to know
(Sheldon:)that she and I are able
to function as friends.
(Penny:)Well, I've never been
friends with any of my exes.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm sure you and Leonard
will be able to pull it off.
(Sheldon:)(phone rings)
(Sheldon:)Oh. It's my friend Amy.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Amy(on skype):)Hi, Sheldon.
(Amy:)I'm just driving home
from my mother's.
(Sheldon:)Did you have a nice time?
(Amy:)I did. Um...
(Amy:)listen, I really enjoyed
spending this morning with you.
(Sheldon:)Well, I can't take
all the credit.
(Sheldon:)It was pretty funny
when that one anchovy
(Sheldon:)started going the wrong way.
(chuckles)
It was.
(Amy:)Uh, listen,
I-I was thinking that, um,
(Amy:)maybe I'm ready
to be your girlfriend again.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)I thought we were just friends.
(Bernadette:)We are.
(Amy:)But I was hoping,
(Amy:)maybe...
Amy,
(Sheldon:)I excel at many things,
(Sheldon:)but getting over you
wasn't one of them.
(Sheldon:)I think I need
to just be your friend.
(Amy:)Okay.
(Amy:)I understand.
(shuddering breath)
(Sheldon:)Good.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I watched a video
(Sheldon:)of the hagfish producing mucus,
(Sheldon:)so I'm gonna change my answer
and eat SpongeBob.
(Amy:)Okay. Sure.